pakistanicelebrities.net 2018-04-24

# Privacy Policy – Pakistani Celebrities

Privacy Policy for www.pakistanicelebrities.net  
If you require any more information please read this or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at admin@pakistanicelebrities.net  
At www.pakistanicelebrities.net, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.pakistanicelebrities.net and how it is used.

Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, www.pakistanicelebrities.net makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.  
Cookies and Web Beacons  
www.pakistanicelebrities.net does not use cookies.  
DoubleClick DART Cookie  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.pakistanicelebrities.net.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.pakistanicelebrities.net and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.pakistanicelebrities.net send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  
www.pakistanicelebrities.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.pakistanicelebrities.net’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.  
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.  
All the data presented in this site has been collected from various sources like Television Shows, Fashion Shows, Internet, Fashion Magazines, personal observations and through people opinion. If you have found any of your data lying here with which you don’t want this site to display kindly report us. As soon as we will receive the mail we will delete those data.please contact on given email address  
for more information on Google’s Cookies policy read here

Contact: admin@pakistanicelebrities.net  
Last Updated:23/01/2018
